// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A tool with a flattened, cross-shaped, or star-shaped tip that fits into the head of a screw to turn it",
    answer: "Screw Driver",
    options: [
      "Screw Driver",
      "Cable Ties",
      "Anti-Static wrist strap",
      "Multitester"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "______________ straps are designed to safely ground operators working with ESD sensitive components, preventing a build-up of static electricity.",
    answer: "Anti-Static wrist strap",
    options: [
      "Screw Driver",
      "Cable Ties",
      "Anti-Static wrist strap",
      "Multitester"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A fastener consisting of a thin, flexible nylon strap with a notched surface, one end of which is threaded through a locking mechanism at the other. It can be used to manage the cables in system unit properly.",
    answer: "Cable Ties",
    options: [
      "Screw Driver",
      "Cable Ties",
      "Anti-Static wrist strap",
      "Multitester"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A _____________ is a measuring instrument that can measure multiple electrical properties.",
    answer: "Multitester",
    options: [
      "Screw Driver",
      "Cable Ties",
      "Anti-Static wrist strap",
      "Multitester"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "It is the first step in disassembling system unit",
    answer: "Unplug your computer and peripheral items",
    options: [
      "Remove side covers",
      "Remove motherboard",
      "Remove Power Supply Unit",
      "Unplug your computer and peripheral items"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "It is the last step in disassembling system unit",
    answer: "Remove motherboard",
    options: [
      "Remove side covers",
      "Remove motherboard",
      "Remove Power Supply Unit",
      "Unplug your computer and peripheral items"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "It is a hand held multipurpose tool used to cut and remove coat of wires and join materials or components by pressing them together.",
    answer: "Crimping Tool",
    options: [
      "LAN Tester",
      "Crimping Tool",
      "Anti-static mat",
      "Multitmeter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It is the first step in assembling system unit",
    answer: "Put back the motherboard",
    options: [
      "Put back the motherboard",
      "Install the memory",
      "Install CPU fan",
      "Put back the side cover"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A _____________ is the main printed circuit board (PCB) in a computer.",
    answer: "Motherboard",
    options: [
      "Random Access Memory",
      "Processor",
      "Motherboard",
      "Optical Disc Drive"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "An ____________ in a computer system allows you to use CDs, DVDs, and Blu-ray discs to listen to music or watch a movie.",
    answer: "Optical Disc Drive",
    options: [
      "Random Access Memory",
      "Processor",
      "Motherboard",
      "Optical Disc Drive"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 11,
    question: "It is a storage device that uses integrated circuit assemblies to store data persistently, typically using flash memory, and functioning as secondary storage in the hierarchy of computer storage",
    answer: "Solid State Drive",
    options: [
      "Solid State Drive",
      "Random Access Memory",
      "Power Supply",
      "Hard Disk Drive"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "This is a type of screwdriver that has pointed edges in the shape of a cross.",
    answer: "Philip screwdriver",
    options: [
      "Hex Screwdriver",
      "Torx screwdriver",
      "Flat head screwdriver",
      "Philip screwdriver"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "This is a type of screwdriver that is tar-shaped and typically used in vehicles, motorcycles, bicycles, computer systems, hard disk drives and consumer electronics.",
    answer: "Torx screwdriver",
    options: [
      "Hex Screwdriver",
      "Torx screwdriver",
      "Flat head screwdriver",
      "Philip screwdriver"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "____________ is a form of computer memory that can be read and changed",
    answer: "Random Access Memory",
    options: [
      "Random Access Memory",
      "Processor",
      "Hard Disk",
      "Optical Disc Drive"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "A magnetic storage medium for a computer. Hard disks are flat circular plates made of aluminum or glass and coated with a magnetic material.",
    answer: "Hard Disk",
    options: [
      "Random Access Memory",
      "Processor",
      "Hard Disk",
      "Optical Disc Drive"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];